Where can we eat?
我们可以去哪吃呢？
Someplace good.
某个好的地方
Someplace cheap.
某个便宜的地方
but vegetarian.
但得是素食的
You're vegetarian, are you?
你是素食主义的，是吗？
Yeah.
是的
I like meat too much to be a vegetarian.
我喜欢肉太多以至于没法做素食主义者.
And fresh fish.
还有新鲜的鱼肉
I don't like fish at all.
我不喜欢鱼肉 一点都不.
And I love bacon. It's my favorite breakfast.
我爱培根.  它是我最爱的早餐
I don't like bacon.
我不喜欢培根
Are you a vegetarian as well?
你是个素食主义者  也？
Me? I don't like vegetables.
我？我不喜欢蔬菜
Elena's not a vegetarian.
Elena不是素食主义者.
She's just a picky eater.
她只是一个挑剔的吃客
Spinach, broccoli, and cauliflower. Ugh.
菠菜(spinach), 西兰花(broccoli) 和菜花(cauliflower) Ugh.
Do you eat cheese?
你吃奶酪吗?
Kevin, I eat anything that can't look at me.
Kevin, 我吃任何东西  那些不能看着我的
How about eggs?
鸡蛋呢?
Oh, I do not like eggs.
Oh, 我不喜欢鸡蛋
Elena, what do you like?
Elena,你喜欢什么?
Coffee.
咖啡.
And coffee.
还有咖啡.
I also like coffee.
我还喜欢咖啡.
Elena even eats coffee yogurt.
Elena甚至吃咖啡奶酪.
And I don't like yogurt.
而我不喜欢吃奶酪.